Finding Aid for the Japanese American Research Project Collection about Japanese in the U.S. (Yuji Ichioka papers) LSC.2010.00
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Personal Papers
  - Masaoka Papers, 1927-1970; 4.5 linear ft.
    Joe Grant Masaoka (1909-1970). Nisei, born in Fresno, California and raised in Salt Lake City, Utah. Regional Director, Japanese American Citizens League (JACL), 1942-1951; Public Relations Consultant, 1951-1964; and Administrator, Japanese American Research Project (JARP) of the University of California, Los Angeles, 1964-1970.
    - Correspondence regarding the Japanese American Research Project (JARP), 1964-1970; 2.0 linear ft.
      - Biographical sketches of Joe G. Masaoka., ca. 1969; (2 items) (Box 121, Folder 1)
      - Alphabetical files of JARP correspondence., 1964-1966 (Box 121, Folder 2-7)
      - Alphabetical files of JARP correspondence., 1967-1969 (Box 122, Folder 1-7)
      - Alphabetical file of JARP correspondence., 1970 (Box 123, Folder 1)
      - Supplementary chronological files of JARP correspondence., 1964-1970 (Box 123, Folder 2-4)
      - Correspondence on the Issei Survey of the Japanese American Research Project, Joe G. Masaoka and Minoru Yasui, Issei Survey Supervisors, Mountain Plains Region., 1964-1967 (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence on the Issei survey., 1964-1966 (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - JARP correspondence exchanged between Franklin D. Murphy, Chancellor, and the Japanese American Research Project., 1962-1968 (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - JARP correspondence exchanged between Gladys Ishida Stone, Director of the Issei Survey, and the Japanese American Research Project., 1962-1967 (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence and other materials on field survey trips of Joe G. Masaoka., 1966-1969 (Box 124, Folder 3)
      - Public relations correspondence of the Japanese American Research Project., 1964-1970 (Box 124, Folder 4-5)
      - Memoranda, JARP Committee, JACL, to JARP., 1962-1969 (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence regarding Course CED 119 on forced removal of which Joe Grant Masaoka was instructor., 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 7)
      - JARP correspondence exchanged between T. Scott Miyakawa, former director of JARP, and the Japanese American Research Project., 1966-1967 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Materials regarding the Japanese American Research Project, 1962-1970; 0.5 linear ft.
      - J.G. Masaoka's reports to the JARP Committee, JACL., July 1963-February 1970; (Ditto., 43 items) (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - JARP news releases written by J.G. Masaoka., April 1964-October 1969; (118 items) (Box 125, Folder 2-4)
      - Miscellaneous documents on the early phase of the Japanese American Research Project (Issei Survey)., 1962-1966; (20 items) (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - Joe Grant Masaoka. "Japanese Americans: Origins, Past and Present"., August 5-8, 1969; (37pp., 2 items) (Box 125, Folder 6)
        A paper presented at the World Conference on Records and Genealogical Seminar held in Salt Lake City, Utah.
      - Joe Grant Masaoka, "The Twain Doth Meet"., 1969; (Manuscript, 10pp., 1 item) (Box 125, Folder 7)
        A play submitted to the Annual Play Contest sponsored by the Auxilliary of the East-West Players Repertory Company.
      - Miscellaneous memos and notes of J.G. Masaoka., (10 items) (Box 125, Folder 8)
      - "In the PC - 25 Years Ago". Clippings from the Pacific Citizen., March 3, 1967-October 10, 1969; (73 pieces) (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Documents and Correspondence regarding the Ishida Land Escheat Case and Claims, 1942-1966; 1.0 linear ft.
      - Statements on the Ishida claim., 1959-1966 (Box 126, Folder 1)
        - Chronology., May 1965; (Manuscript, 2 pp.) (Box 126, Folder 1)
        - The claim of Sue Ishida., November 1966; (Manuscript, 17 pp.) (Box 126, Folder 1)
        - Before the State Board of Control: Synopsis of Claim of Sue Ishida., 1959; (Manuscript, 6 pp.) (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - Clerk's transcripts on appeal. Sue Ishida vs Smallpage, appeal from the judgment of the Superior Court of the State of California in and for the County of Sacramento, in the District Court of Appeal, Third Appellate District of the State of California., (Manuscripts, 2 volumes, 2 items) (Box 126, Folder 2)
      - Statements, records and other documents regarding the claim of Sue Ishida before the State Board of Control of the State of California., 1959-1966; (26 items) (Box 126, Folder 3)
      - Copies of documentary evidence assembled for the filing of the claim before the State Board of Control, California., 1922-1955; (82 items) (Box 126, Folder 4)
      - Documents regarding the Winafred Orchards in Modesto, California, jointly owned by Henry R. Ishida and Lafayette J. Smallpage. (Box 126, Folder 5-9)
        - Copies of legal documents on the probate of the estate of the late Henry R. Ishida, and the Alien Land Escheat Case filed against the Winafred Orchards., 1941-1942; (29 items) (Box 126, Folder 5)
        - Smallpage's grant deeds and a bank statement of his account., 1943-1944; (6 items, photostat copies) (Box 126, Folder 6)
        - Smallpage's financial deeds on the Vaccaro Ranch (Winafred Orchards)., 1926; (3 items, photostat copies) (Box 126, Folder 7)
        - Copies of annual financial statements and reports on the Winafred Orchards., 1922, 1926-1928, 1932-1935 and 1937-1941; (13 items) (Box 126, Folder 8)
        - Transcripts of interviews with Gladys and Sue Ishida., April 1942; (Manuscripts, 3 items) (Box 126, Folder 9)
          regarding The Winafred Orchards and contents of the safe deposit box #13 of the late Henry R. Ishida.
      - Copies of court papers and statements regarding the Ishida Alien Land Escheat Case and Ishida's postwar claims on the case., 1942-1955; (15 items) (Box 126, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous memos and notes regarding the Ishida claim., (30 items) (Box 126, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence exchanged between J.G. Masaoka and the Ishidas (Gladys and Sue Ishida) on the claim., June 1951-December 1961; (45 letters) (Box 127, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence regarding the Ishida claim., January 1948-July 1966; (207 letters) (Box 127, Folder 2)
      - An album on the Ishida claim, compiled by J.G. Masaoka., ca. 1960; (1 notebook) (Box 127, Folder 3)
        Contains correspondence and other documents regarding the claim.
      - Bills and receipts on the handling of the Ishida claim., July 1951-February 1958; (32 pieces) (Box 127, Folder 4)
      - Documents, records and court papers on the Alien Land Law claims., ca. 1950-1952; (28 items) (Box 127, Folder 5)
      - George Ochikubo et al. vs Charles Hartwell Bonesteel. (Box 127, Folder 6)
        - Memorandum of George Ochikubo et al. vs Charles Hartwell Bonesteel, United States District Court in and for the Southern District of California, Central Division., 1945; (Mimeographed, 37pp. + 38pp., 1 item) (Box 127, Folder 6)
        - The full text of Mr. Justice Murphy's dissenting opinion. The United States Supreme Court., December 18, 1944.; (5pp. Mimeographed, 1 item) (Box 127, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous clippings on the Alien Land Law claims., 1951-1966; (10 items) (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Documents, Records and Correspondence regarding Masaoka Associates, 0.5 linear ft.
      - Masaoka Associates. Report on the Alien Land Laws in the United States. San Francisco., 1951; (Manuscript, 95pp. Carbon copy, 1 item) (Box 128, Folder 1)
      - Masaoka Associates. Report on Naturalization and Immigration of Japanese in the United States. San Francisco., 1951; (Manuscript, 67pp. Carbon copy, 1 item) (Box 128, Folder 2)
      - Documents and correspondence regarding the Redevelopment Agency of the City of Richmond, California, and George and Tom Oishi's Forced Removal Claim against said agency. (Box 128, Folder 3-7)
        - Documents regarding the Redevelopment Agency of the City of Richmond, California., 1957-1961; (17 items) (Box 128, Folder 3)
        - Appraiser's reports on the properties owned by Tom and Shizue Oishi in Richmond, California., March-April 1961; (6 items) (Box 128, Folder 4)
        - Documents regarding the forced removal claim of Oishi brothers against the Redevelopment Agency., 1961-1962; (18 items) (Box 128, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence regarding the Oishi brothers' forced removal claim., December 1960-January 1964; (74 letters) (Box 128, Folder 6)
        - Photographs of the Oishi Nursery., n.d.; (12 pieces) (Box 128, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence regarding Masaoka Associates., 1945-1963; (13 items) (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Assorted Legal Briefs, 0.5 linear ft.
      - Smallpage vs Ishida, 3 Civil no. 8946. (Box 129)
        - Appellant's opening brief, District Court of Appeal, State of California., February 1956 (Box 129)
        - Respondent's reply brief, District Court of Appeal, State of California., April 1956 (Box 129)
        - Appellant's closing brief, District Court of Appeal, State of California., July 1956 (Box 129)
        - Brief of Amicus Curiae, JACL, in support of contention of appellant Sue Ishida., September 1957 (Box 129)
        - Appellant's petition for a hearing by the Supreme Court, the Supreme Court of the State of California., November 1957 (Box 129)
        - Respondent's answer to appellant's petition for a hearing by the Supreme Court., December 1957 (Box 129)
      - Sei Fujii vs the State of California, 2nd Civil no. 17309. (Box 129)
        - Appellant's opening brief, District Court of Appeal, State of California., n.d. (Box 129)
        - Petition for hearing, Supreme Court of the State of California., June 1950 (Box 129)
      - Oyama vs the People of the State of California, L.A. no. 19533. (Box 129)
        - Appellant's opening brief, Supreme Court of the State of California. (Box 129)
        - Respondent's brief, Supreme Court of the State of California. (Box 129)
        - Appellant's reply brief, Supreme Court of the State of California. (Box 129)
        - Brief of Amicus Curiae, in support of appellants, Supreme Court of the State of California. (Box 129)
        - Petition for rehearing, Supreme Court of the State of California. (Box 129)
      - Torao Takahashi vs Fish and Game Commission, Los Angeles no. 19835. (Box 129)
        - Respondent's brief, Supreme Court of the State of California. (Box 129)
      - Masaokas vs the People of the State of California, Los Angeles no. 21479. (Box 129)
        - Appellant's opening brief, Supreme Court of the State of California., June 1950 (Box 129)
        - Brief for respondents, Supreme Court of the State of California., August 1950 (Box 129)
        - Application of respondents for leave to file additional brief; and brief, Supreme Court of the State of California. (Box 129)
        - Supplemental brief of respondents, Supreme Court of the State of California. (Box 129)
        - Appellant's closing brief, Supreme Court of the State of California., December 1950 (Box 129)
      - Sonoda vs the United States of America, no.67-58. (Box 129)
        - Opinion, United States Court of Claims., June 1961 (Box 129)
      - Korematsu vs United States of America, no.10248. (Box 129)
        - Opinion, United States Circuit Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit., December 1943 (Box 129)
      - John T. Regan vs Cameron King, no.10299. (Box 129)
        - Brief for JACL, Amicus Curiae. (Box 129)
      - Hirabayashi vs United States of America, no.10308. (Box 129)
        - Opinion, United States Circuit Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit., March 1943 (Box 129)
      - Hideichi Takeguma, Yasuto Fujioka and Kingo Tajii vs United States of America, no.11079. (Box 129)
        - Appellant's opening brief, United States Circuit Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit. (Box 129)
      - United States of America vs Tadayasu Abo et al., no.12251; and United States of America vs Mary Kaname Furuya et al., no.122252. (Box 129)
        - Brief for appellants, United States Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit. (Box 129)
      - Hirabayashi vs United States of America, no.870; and Yasui vs United States of America, no.871. (Box 129)
        - Brief Amicus Curiae, JACL, Supreme Court of the United States of America., October 1942 (Box 129)
      - Fred Toyozaburo Korematsu vs United States of America, no.22. (Box 129)
        - Brief for the United States, Supreme Court of the United States, October Term., 1944 (Box 129)
        - Brief for the American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), Amicus Curiae, Supreme Court of the United States, October Term., 1944 (Box 129)
        - Brief of JACL, Amicus Curiae, Supreme Court of the United States, October Term., 1944 (Box 129)
      - Fred Y. Oyama and Kajiro Oyama vs State of California, no.44. (Box 129)
        - Brief for petitioners, Supreme Court of the United States, October Term., 1947 (Box 129)
        - Brief of Amicus Curiae in support of appellants, Civil Rights Defense Union of Northern California, Supreme Court of the United States, October Term., 1947 (Box 129)
        - Opinion of the court delivered by Mr. Chief Justice Vinson, Supreme Court of the United States, October Term., 1947 (Box 129)
      - James M. Hurd and Mary I. Hurd vs Frederic E. Hodge et al., no.290. (Box 129)
        - Brief of the JACL, Amicus Curiae, Supreme Court of the United States, October Term., 1947 (Box 129)
      - Richard Perry Loving, et al. vs Commonwealth of Virginia, no.395. (Box 129)
        - Brief of Amici Curiae, JACL, Supreme Court of the United States, October Term., 1966 (Box 129)
      - Taro Takahashi vs Fish and Game Commission, no.533. (Box 129)
        - Petition for a writ of certiorari to the Supreme Court of California, Supreme Court of the United States, October Term., 1947 (Box 129)
        - Memorandum for the United States as Amicus Curiae in support of the petition for a writ of certiorari, Supreme Court of the United States, October Term., 1947 (Box 129)
        - Brief for Amici Curiae, Surpeme Court of the United States, October Term., 1947 (Box 129)
        - Brief of the JACL, Amicus Curiae, Supreme Court of the United States, October Term., 1947 (Box 129)
        - Opinion of the Court delivered by Mr. Justice Black, Supreme Court of the United States, October Term., 1947 (Box 129)
      - Fred Oyama and Kajiro Oyama vs State of California, no.1059. (Box 129)
        - Petition for a writ of certiorari to the Supreme Court of California, Supreme Court of the United States, October Term., 1946 (Box 129)
  - Matsumoto Papers, 1941; 1 folder
    Tsuyoshi Matsumoto. Biography unknown.
    - The Japanese in California: an account of their contributions to the growth and development of the state and of their part in the community life., 1941; (53pp. Carbon copy, 1 item) (Box 160, Folder 15)
      A report prepared for the Welfare Committee of the Central Japanese Association of America.
  - McGovern Papers, 1942-1945; 5.0 linear ft.
    Melvin P. McGovern. High school teacher and reports officer, Granada Relocation Center, Amache, Colorado.
    - Documents and records on the Merced Assembly Center and the Granada Relocation Center., 0.5 linear ft.
      - A report on the education department of the Merced Assembly Center., (Manuscript, 6pp., carbon copy) (Box 113, Folder 1)
      - Documents on the Granada Project, War Relocation Authority (WRA)., 1942-1945; (6 items) (Box 113, Folder 2)
        - A brief description of the War Relocation Authority Project (the Granada Relocation Center) for Evacuated Japanese Americans at Amache, Colorado., n.d.; (Manuscript, 4pp. Carbon copy) (Box 113, Folder 2)
        - Granada Relocation Center Charter., n.d.; (4pp., mimeographed) (Box 113, Folder 2)
          Marked 1st draft in red pencil.
        - Charter., n.d.; (4pp., mimeographed) (Box 113, Folder 2)
        - A map of the Granada Relocation Area., n.d.; (1p., mimeographed) (Box 113, Folder 2)
        - Appointed Personnel, War Relocation Authority Granada Project, a roster., March 1, 1945; (4pp., mimeographed) (Box 113, Folder 2)
        - War Relocation Authority, Granada Project, chronological History, June 1942-August 1945., n.d. [ca. 1945]; (Manuscript, 43 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 2)
      - Report filled out by the Granada War Relocation Authority for the Spanish Consulate of San Francisco on the visit of Spanish Consul F. de Amat to the Granada Relocation Center., July 7, 1944; (Mimeographed, 16pp., 2 items) (Box 113, Folder 3)
        Appends documentary exhibits.
      - Quarterly reports on the Granada Relocation Center., 1942-1943; (4 items) (Box 113, Folder 4)
        - Quarterly Report of the Granada Relocation Center, War Relocation Authority, Amache, Colorado., July 1-September 30, 1942; 41pp. Mimeographed, 1 item) (Box 113, Folder 4)
        - 3 manuscripts of the Quarterly reports of the Granada Relocation Center., December 31, 1942 and March 31 & June 30, 1943; (57pp. + 40pp. + 16pp. Carbon copies, 3 items) (Box 113, Folder 4)
      - Manuscripts of the Final Reports of the Granada War Relocation Authority Project for various divisions and their activities, prepared by the persons in charge., 1945 (Box 113, Folder 5-8)
        - Personal Narrative Report of the Reports Officer, Granada Relocation Center. Prepared by Joe McClelland, Reports Officer, and Melvin P. McGovern, Acting Reports Officer., August 13, 1942-April 15, 1945; (Manuscript, 53pp. + appendix. 30pp. + 8pp. + appendix. 7pp. Carbon copy, 1 item) (Box 113, Folder 5)
        - Internal Security: Final Report Prepared According to Handbook Release #199, Section 140.10.IB, Exhibit XXVI. Compiled by Forrest G. Foster, Acting Chief, Internal Security Section, Community Management Division, Granada Relocation Center., (Manuscript, 10pp. + appendix. Carbon copy, 1 item) (Box 113, Folder 6)
        - Business Enterprises: Final Report Prepared According to Handbook Release #199, Section 140.10.IB, Exhibit XVI. Compiled by W. Ray Johnson, Chief, Project Community Management, Granada Relocation Center., (Manuscript, 24pp. + 11pp. + appendix. Carbon copy [1 item]) (Box 113, Folder 7)
        - Community Government: Final Report Prepared According to Handbook Release #199, Section 140.10.IB, Exhibit XXVI. Compiled by W. Ray Johnson, Chief, Project Management, Granada Relocation Center., (Manuscript, 33pp. + appendix. Carbon copy, 1 item) (Box 113, Folder 8)
      - Copies of the reports prepared by the staff of the Reports Office, Documentary Section, Granada Relocation Center., December 1942-August 1943 (Box 113, Folder 9-11)
        - Community Council., December 23, 1942; (12 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Farm Section Report, by Mark H. Hayashi., December 31, 1942; (20 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Water and Electric Power System, confidential., January 8, 1943; (7 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Coordinating Council., January 13, 1943; (7 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Housing, by Housing Superintendent., January 13, 1943; (5pp. + 4 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Amache Little Theater - Outing., January 18, 1943; (2 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - The Hospital Christmas Party., January 18, 1943; (6 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Laboratory Department of the Amache Hospital., January 18, 1943; (6 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Baby Food Station., January 20, 1943; (7 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Fire Department., January 25, 1943; (7 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Individual Mannerisms., January 30, 1943; (9 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Nisei Need Assurance of...., January 30, 1943; (5 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - WRA Hospital Monthly Report., January 31, 1943; (7 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - The First Semester in Amache Elementary and Secondary Schools., February 4, 1943; (6 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Post Office., February 4, 1943; (3 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - The Dental Department., February 8, 1943; (7 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Dr. [G.D. Carlyle] Thompson Visits Amache Hospital., February 8, 1943; (5 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Amache School Controversy., February 9, 1943; (14 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Findings, Agricultural Labor Problems., February 10, 1943; (11pp. + appendix) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - WRA Hospital, Optometry Department., February 10, 1943; (4 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Transportation., February 15, 1943; (8 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Block Managers., February 17, 1943; (5 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Buddhism in America., February 19, 1943; (6 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Sei Ch no Ie., February 19, 1943; (5 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - The School Libraries., February 26, 1943; (4 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - Survey of Outside Employment., February 28, 1943; (2pp. + appendix) (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - College Council., March 1, 1943; (11 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Juvenile Delinquency., March 1, 1943; (8 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Pharmacy., March 2, 1943; (3pp. + appendix) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Non-Christian Religious Activities., March 3, 1943; (3 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Highlights from the Documentation Staff Meeting., March 8, 1943; (2 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Documentation Section., March 9, 1943; (4 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Hospital Warehouse & Property Division., March 10, 1943; (3 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Poultry Report., March 12, 1943; (5 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Temporary Community Council., March 18, 1943; (6 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - The Army Registration and Nisei Loyalty, confidential., March 17, 1943; (5 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Visit of the Spanish Vice-Consul., March 17, 1943; (10 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Public Relations: Girl Reserve Conference., March 24, 1943; (2 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Voluntary Enlistment., March 24, 1943; (2 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Evacuee School Teachers., March 24, 1943; (5 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Typical Reasons Given for Changing Answers to Question no. 28 from 'No' to 'Yes'., March 25, 1943; (2 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Opinions on Registration: Volunteer Attitudes., March 30, 1943; (4 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Public Relations: Education Department., April 2, 1943; (4 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Reaction to WRA Relocation Program., April 2, 1943; (2 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - WRA Farm Report: Hog Project., April 2, 1943; (4 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Documentation., April 5, 1943; (11 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Community Council., April 6, 1943; (4 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Community Government., April 1, 1943; (3 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Reaction on the All-Nisei Combat Unit., April 6, 1943; (5 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Education: Semester of High School and Scholastic Results., April 10, 1943; (4 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Hospital Cafeteria and Kitchen, by Yoshiaki Sugita., April 12, 1943; (4 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - WRA Farm Report: Vegetable Project., April 14, 1943; (9 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - OSYA Training Program., April 14, 1943; (2 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Politics: Block Managers., April 14, 1943; (5pp. + appendix) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Attitude toward Administration Officials., April 28, 1943; (2 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Documentation Staff Meeting., April 20, 1943; (1p.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Coordinating Council Conference on Community Improvement., April 24, 1943; (9 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - WRA Farm Report: Grain and Feed Crop Project., April 27, 1943; (5 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Attitude., April 27, 1943; (4 pp.) (Box 113, Folder 10)